[Last Episode]
Let go! I can go alone!
Then go
Hey. Did you let go because I told you to?
-Grab me again
-Okay, I'm grabbing again
Let go, you jerk!
How can you do this to me?! How could you?
How could you do that to me?
How could you?
I was wrong
What?
I doubted you and i considered your devotion a small thing.
I forgot that you are so precious to me. I judged you objectively leaving you alone.
I broke the promise of being with you forever
I'm sorry.
- Did you just surrender?
- Yeah, i did.
You making go crazy. You surrendered too quickly.
It's not that quick. The moment you walked out of this room, i thought of doing that.
How could you turn your back at me? Even if it's my fault, you should forgive me!
It felt like being left alone in the world.
It was selfish.
I thought my kid's hapinness comes first.
I'm a selfish woman.
But, do i have to be criticized by my family?
I was really lonely for a few days
I can understand if my child criticizes me because he is just my son.
But, you should be different.
-You are on my side
-Forgive me...
I forgot that you must never be judged by me.
How could you forget about that? I felt like my heart is torning apart.
- I'm sorry...
- Do you know what Jung Hoon told me?
He said he had a mental breakdown and his mental breakdown was beacause of me!
He asked me who i really am and what kind of person i am.
He doeasn't understand why i'm against of his marriage.
You're family disapproved of me too
You didn't understand then either
He's going to leave us eventually. How many times did i tell you, that your lifetime companion is me, not him?
You must let Jung Hoon live his own life.
While raising him.. We taught him all the know-hows we learned while living.
It's his choice to keep those lessons or not.
- We should respect him.
- I know.
I know that, but i can't just do that!
Yeah, i know. Can't we just let him go?
Let me help you get up now.
-I'm drunk!
-I know
You should get drunk sometimes. You look so lovely!
-Honey. Honey! Honey!
-Do you want to lie down now?
-Yes
-Mom, are you okay?
Drink some water
Welcome back, buddy.
Am i your friend? I regret that i raised you so democratically.
Wipe your hands
How sweet of you. Why did i raise you like this?
If i had raised you wrong, i would've been willing to give you to someone else.
Mom...
I don't want to see you anymore so get out
-I'm sorry
-What?
For everything that hurt you during the wedding preparation.
But, you should know this. You are the one and only mother for me.
And nobody can replace you.
- You evil bastard.
- Mrs Jung it's not you.
You can't compare with her. You stupid mom.
But there are things you can say and things you can't say.
I like you mom. I like that you're my mom.
- I hate you though.
- I love you.
- I don't love you.
- Ah...stop playing hard to get!
- I'm not playing hard to get.
- Yes you are.
You are so good at it. You say, "i hate you", "i don't want to see you", but you don't mean it.
- Honey...
- Now, this is the real you.
You get out. I want to spend some time with my husband.
Sleep tight tonight. I know you are stressed beacause of her.
You were stressed too.
Goodnight. Goodnight mom.
You should get punished for getting me stressed those couple of days.
I'll understand even if you don't come to my wedding.
I don't want him to go away. I don't want to let him go.
-Why are you coming out?
-I'll do it.
-No, I'll do it. They said to be careful in the early stages of the pregnancy.
-You like it that much?
-I do
Saying it once won't do. "I like it, I like it, I like it."
I'll get it.
You're here?
How could you do that to me? I trusted you!
- Deul Rae is pregnant!
- What?
She's pregnant. I'm going to become a dad!
-Alright, that's that..
-You're here?
-Yes, aunt... I mean sister-in-law
-Did you eat breakfast?
-Not yet.
-Wait here, I'll prepare it for you.
-I'll do it!
Don't make a big deal about this. I'm fine.
- She is right about that!
- She always says the right thing.
I think I can do a good living if i listen to her.
I made fun of you when you said she's a femme fatale before,
I think she is a femme fatale. You got whipped by a woman and put your younger brother in a tight spot. How can you do this to me?
Still, I sent the money back to your account. I didn't give that money to the niece.
You take care of it. Whether you will split the money with her or you will keep it, do as you wish.
This is not a matter of you simply transferred the money to my account and didn't give it to my wife, so it won't lead to much loss on my part.
You are the one I trust the most in the world.
I am angry at the fact that you didn't fully have my back and threw me aside for your wife.
I thought you are my person till the end. But you weren't.
Then what can I do? She asked if you are she comes first.
So I didn't answer and she locked the bedroom door for couple days and wouldn't even open it for me.
As soon as she found out that she's pregnant, instead of rejoicing, she asked who comes first.
I had no choice but lose in this fight.
What if she leaves?
You won't leave me but women can.
I like it now. I'm happy.
I even have a kid that I didn't even think of.
Isn't this a mira-
-Sorry
-It's fine. As long as you're happy, it's fine.
I knew you'd be like this. I knew you'd understand.
It's not like I am completely understanding. I have a hole in my heart.
I have no one next to me anymore.
Do Hyun come in. Let's eat. You too, honey.
Okay.. Come in.
Eat
-What are you doing?
-Good thing you came mom.
I want to buy a bed, but should it be a queen or king size?
I think if I buy a king size, it will fill up the whole room.
- What's the difference?
- About 20cm.
-What about the price?
-Around $100
Buy the king size. The room is small, but you should sleep comfortably.
- Jung Hoon is lengthy.
- If I put the bed in, what should I do with the desk?
Ah! The room is too small.
You could put it in Deul Rae's room and use both rooms.
- Deul Rae is just saying it. She won't come here all that often.
- I better look at Aunt's room once more.
Why isn't she contacting me?
Jung Hoon's mom. Are you really going to let them live with me?
It's about time you should say "I was wrong. I will buy you a condo and I can't have my son live with the in-laws", isn't it?
-What time is it?
-You can sleep more.
-It smells good
-Here
I want to drink it later
Let's go on a vacation.
It's been too long since we had some alone time.
Since we lived together for almost 30 years, I thought we had a secure indestructible relationship.
But from this incident, I realized that it's not true.
There is no such thing as a secure relationship.
Like how we tried to keep this relationship working,
we have to keep trying until we die.
I realized it this time around too that kids won't always follow my wish.
No matter how much I tell him, he won't listen.
I guess he needs to go through it himself and suffer.
I already booked the flight for 3 nights and 4 days at Hookkaido.
-You're going to go with me, right?
-If I'm not by your side, then who would be?
Min Ho developed gluttony lately.
-Do you want more rice?
-It's okay. It's already my second bowl.
This dude. It's all because you feel void inside.
Why are you crying? I am the one who feels like crying.
You're the one who pushed me into the corner.
I don't understand why I keep on tearing up like this.
As a man gets older his estrogen levels go up.
It's because you are getting emotional lately.
Honey, still, don't say I am old.
I am 43 years old now, so by the time our kid enters elementary school, I will be 51 years old.
What if our kid hates it because I'm old?
Even if you're old, you still can't compare to my age.
By the time our kid is in 3rd grade, I will be 60.
You're right. Compared to that, I am so young.
Oh, you're so simple. Are you happy that your wife will be 60?
It' still better than me turning 60 years old.
Right. I would have thought the same if I was younger than you.
By the way, you two, is it alright to be like that with a guest?
I am sorry Do Hyun. It pains my heart to think about you.
Seriously, why are you being like this? I can't get used to it.
Like how a pregnant woman can't control her emotions due to the hormones, you're feelings are up and down.
Nephew-in-law. You shouldn't call me like that anymore.
Fine, if you get divorced, I am not Aunt anymore.
Then Mr. Nam Do Hyun. Why do keep on picking on my husband?
Pardon?
I was just listening from earlier, but it seems like you're kind of picking on my husband.
- You're not upset, honey?
- No, I am not.
- But why am I upset?
- However, if I were in your shoes, I would have felt the same way.
Hyung!
I am sorry, Do Hyun. But I am like this. She has me wrapped around her finger, but what can I do?
- I am leaving.
- Good bye.
- I won't see you out.
- Do Hyun.
You need to have dessert before you leave. If you leave like this, I won't be at peace.
Live well with the sister-in-law. I am holding it in since you're happy.
- Do Hyun.
- What!
Can't you be happy too?
I am in a good place but it seems like I am the only one in a good place, so I feel sorry for you.
I won't be where I am now if it weren't for you.
I wanted to die many times.
But you were my rock.
I thought I will never get a chance to be happy.
I am thankful to you. If I died back then, such a day won't be here for me.
Stop saying nonsense and if you're happy now, enjoy your happiness to the fullest.
Don't cry!
I am changing. I am falling apart. I am becoming a worse person.
You must like it... that it turned out how you wanted.
I think the one before this one was better.
- I like this better.
- I like the one before better as well.
Then choose that one.
It's our marriage, why would you wear the dress Dong Bi likes?
The bride's wedding dress is not something that is supposed to please the groom.
It's for the bride and the bride's guests.
Does the groom have wits intact to check out the dress?
Then let's go with the one you wore earlier and ask the shop to have it fitted.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Both of you stand, I'll take a picture.
We are supposed to stop by Ki Joong's restaurant afterwards. You should come too.
I told you to stand.
Are you not going to go?
I'm not going. I'm busy.
Even if you are busy, you don't even have time to stop by briefly to see his face?
I don't.
Did something happen between you and Ki Joong's mother?
Did you meet my aunt?
- I met her.
- My aunt is no joke.
I almost died from being scared. Compared to your mom, she's 100 times scarier.
She is a hundred times scarier compared to my mother-in-law?
What will you do?
What will I do? It's my mom and my aunt and I have say bad things about them behind their backs?
I'm sorry.
It's alright. People talk bad things about even the President behind his back.
Mom's nothing.
You guys leave. It's about time you leave seeing you being lovey-dovey.
We see each other often.
Hyung, come here. I came to give you something.
What is it that you wanted to give me?
We got back together after breaking up twice. We will never let go of each other's hand for the rest of our lives. Groom: Ha Jung Hoon. Bride: Jung Hye Yoon
We got back together after breaking up twice. You're showing off about this?
We are showing off. Do you know how difficult it is to get back together after a break up?
If we didn't break up, we wouldn't have known how precious we were to each other.
So you should approach Dong Bi first.
- What do you mean?
- You fought with Dong Bi.
When I told Dong Bi she should come to see you, she said she didn't want to.
As a person who has gone through it, I'm telling you this. It's better to make up quickly.
It seems like whenever you guys see me, you start lecturing about relationships.
I don't think there is a guy worth getting while harming and damaging myself.
Minnie Don Bi
What's up?
What do you mean? You should do a good job if I gave you a project.
Is the brochure complete? Why aren't you bringing it?
I'll give it to you.
-I'll going to your house.
-No, I'll go to the restaurant.
You keep on doing peculiar things lately and sway me, so this won't do.
Doing peculiar things?
What's the next schedule?
We have to tell your mom about walking you down the isle.
I'll tell her when I get home.
No, tell her officially when I am present.
That's the polite thing to do.
If you tell her by yourself, she might take it lightly.
To tell you the truth, I haven't heard of the bride walking down the aisle holding their mother's hand.
-It won't be easy for her.
- Alright. Thank you.
I like it that you say 'thank you' and 'sorry' a lot.
In return, I could be bit**.
You know your place as well.
You are telling me to walk down the aisle holding hands with you?
Yes.
I have never heard of a mother going down the aisle holding their daughter's hand.
I thought it was weird at first too but I thought about it and I think it's a good idea.
I don't want to. What will other people say?
When did you care what other people think?
You're the one who always talk about common sense. It is a common sense to walk down the isle with your mom?
My common sense loses to non common sense. I don't see why not.
Forget it. I'm not doing it.
Then who will do it?
You two just hold hands. I have seen many marriages where the bride and groom enter holding hands.
You should do it. It's perfect for you. It fits your personality.
How does it fit my personality?
- Pushing yourself forward.
- Hey!
Anyways I'm entering with you.
I told you I don't want to! What bizzare things you are making me do!
Doesn't your mother talk about meeting me?
She went travelling with my father.
By now, it's about time she comes to make peace.
Really? Is she still against the marriage?
I am sorry, Mother-in-law. In return, I am moving into your house.
This is not going the way I planned.
Don't we have to paper the walls in our room?
We have to paper the walls.
Do it with your money. I gave you the savings account.
Alright. It's money that I can't use...
- Then give it back.
- I'm just saying.
Why should I give it back?
We have one more thing to take care of.
We should go look for wallpaper?
How is it that we're on the same page like this.
Look at these two.
It will be fun to see your couple next to Deul Rae couple.
Are you going somewhere?
Oh, I want to see sister-in-law, rather your niece.
Why? Do Hyun is in the back of your mind?
Yes, he's my younger brother.
I feel like I acted in a way I shouldn't have because of you.
It's not something you shouldn't have done. It was a good thing.
To start off, it was nasty of Do Hyun.
Don't use words like nasty. Our kid is listening.
The kid has a right to hear every single word.
In this rough world, he will hear more criticisms than praises. He needs to get trained beforehand.
- You're right.
- Exactly.
If you meet Hye Jin, don't tell her about my pregnancy.
- Why not?
- I want it to be a surprise. A surprise party.
Alright. My lips are sealed.
Why is she asking me to do such a thing?
Oh, what's that.
Deul Rae always calls at times like this.
- What?
- Sis.
Why are you acting cute? Save it for your husband.
We will go over to your place this evening, let's have dinner together.
Ask the kids to be there too. I have an announcement.
Don't bring your husband.
I became his priority.
What do you mean priority?
I became the most important person to Min Ho.
So what? He will obey your words?
He's already obeying my words. We already took care of Hye Jin's problem.
How?
I will tell you later. I have an announcement to make at dinner. So everyone has to be there
Okay? I will see you later then.
What kind of announcement does she need to make? Also, how did she handle Hye Jin's problem?
Never mind the announcement. Tell me how you took care of Hye Jin's problem.
What are you doing here, Uncle?
I have something to say. Sister-in-law. Today, I am not here as your uncle but as your brother-in-law.
Does Do Hyun come home often lately?
Yes. He wouldn't move out.
I guess he doesn't want to move out.
Can't you give Do Hyun another chance?
He has a bit of obsessive compulsive disorder. His family only acknowledges if you rank the first place.
So he had a difficult childhood.
There is a 7 year old kid inside him and he can't help it so he throws tantrums like that.
Can't you pretend your his mom and give him another chance?
He's not the only one who has a kid at heart.
I had to be mature when I was growing up too so I didn't have a proper childhood either.
When I think about Do Hyun, my heart is in pain.
He's acting like that because he's lonely.
Once he goes astray, he has tendency to continue on that wrong path,
and because you don't like him, he's continues go astray even more.
If you comfort him, he wouldn't be like that.
Right now, it's difficult for me to even take care of myself.
I am overwhelmed taking care of myself and Tae Won
He has you. He depends on you a lot, Uncle.
The money in the alias account, I transferred it back to Do Hyun's account.
He will totally feel betrayed by me.
He came to see me this morning and after seeing me happy because of Deul Rae's pregnancy, he just left.
He's a nice person like that.
Aunt is pregnant?
Oh my goodness. She told me to keep it a secret.
She said she will announce it later at the family gathering.
All the good things are happening to Aunt lately.
- Can you keep it a secret?
- Congratulations, Uncle.
If the money in alias account has all been transferred back to Mr. Nam Do Hyun's account,
that is subject to division of assets.
That's a good news.
At the next court appointed date, I will request that account to be verified again.
Jung Hye Jin's lawyer will request for that account to be verified at the next court appointed date.
Then your hidden assets will be revealed.
You're saying that's subject to division of assets as a community property?
Yes.
That's let's summarize our case.
Who has the advantage right now?
Mrs. Jung Hye Jin.
How can you say that without any hesitation?
I told you from the start.
You have a fatal liability.
Civil Code Article 840 Section 1, cheating by the spouse. But you are not able to overcome that now.
I could insist that I didn't cheat at the trial.
If my husband continues to deny that he cheated, will the court accept that?
These days, if the spouse even frequently texts someone other than his spouse,
that is accepted as a cheating behavior.
But Nam Do Hyun's actions were worse than that.
Then I could rest assured about proving the cheating part.
Right. I have someone tailing him now too.
Even though I told Mr. Nam Do Hyun that we have more than enough evidence to prove his cheating behavior,
but it's better to be safe.
He continues to visit that model's home. It will be difficult for him to deny his cheating behavior.
Thank you.
How about my excessive spending issue?
As we have discussed at the arbitration, I don't think your excessive spending issue will be very problematic.
Even the part about how he was abused by his mother-in-law. How will he prove that?
That will create headache for him.
In a case such as this, how will the division of assets be?
Since we have the upper hand with the cheating spouse,
the court will side with us.
Will I get the custody for sure as well?
I don't know what the report of the earlier child psychological evaluation will state and how it will be to your advantage,
custody of the 7 year old is usually granted to the mom.
So I have no advantage in this trial whatsoever.
You knew this already from the start when you started this process.
To cut to the chase, you started this to torment Mrs. Jung Hye Jin.
Since you don't want to just give her to money, weren't you going to pay only after making her go through a hard time?
Once you go to the trial,
I will raise the injustice about how Mr. Nam Do Hyun is the one with the liability as the cheating spouse but he is the one who initiated this litigation.
- Will they take that into the consideration?
- Yes, the court is not oblivious.
He acted in a despicable manner. It's obvious.
Even though he was the one who misbehaved, he tried to blame it on the other person to avoid the crisis.
Especially to a wife who he lived with for a long time.
That's no good.
I think it would be best for you to settle at this point.
Even if you go to trial, nothing will be to your advantage.
I cannot give up on the custody of the child.
Then let's talk about this again once the report for the psychological evaluation is available.
What if the report is to my wife's advantage?
Jung Hye Jin will get the custody.
That what kind of right about the child do I have?
You have visitation rights.
I understand.
Please let me know once the evaluation report is available.
Yes, then I will leave.
I brought it. I will leave as soon as you see it.
My pride is hurt.
What about it?
I am only worth that much to you?
That sounds familiar.
It's what you said to me.
Does it feel nice to have it repeated to you?
It don't dislike it.
You don't know my worth yet but there are many things about me that I haven't shown you yet.
Once you see them, you'll change your mind.
Show it to an another girl.
Oh, you need this too.
What are you doing?
I am matching my steps with yours.
There was this side to you?
I have many layers you don't know yet.
Why are you acting like this, pressuring me? Hurry and go back in?
I don't like it, do it over.
- You didn't even look at it.
- Even if I hadn't looked at it, I don't like it.
You're being unreasonable. Fine. I will do it over and bring it.
Where are you going?
I said I will redo it and bring it.
- How can I trust that?
- Then what should I do?
Do it in front of me, while I am watching.
I will watch to see if you do a good job or not.
You're become really weird. Why are you acting lame like this?
Just be your cool self. I can't get used to this.
I wanted to be like this.
I wanted to lean on you but instead, I pushed you away.
I missed you but I acted like I didn't.
Because I was afraid you'd look down on me if I am immature, so instead of showing you my immature side,
I pretended to be cool.
Don't say such things. I waver then.
I am telling you this so you could waiver, so you should waiver.
Don't cast me aside.
I don't want to force sacrifice on your part.
However, what can I do? I cannot throw away my family.
Still, I could keep my distance from them.
I am not as courageous as you are.
I cannot not throw away the privileges my family allows me to enjoy.
I am not as strong as you.
I am much weaker and much more foolish.
I am sorry.
I am sorry. I cannot let you go.
I don't want to let you go.
It's been so long since we spent time like this.
Yeah.
It's nice.
Should we just live together?
Let's just live together instead of marrying.
Then we don't have to get bound by our family.
That's a very difficult decision for a woman seeking security.
I am saying let's go back to how things were in the beginning.
Let's just find our way and live according to it.
Since I changed my mind mid way and you made stupid moves,
let's return to our proper place.
It needs an upgrade.
Why are we here?
I don't want my woman to be in the shadows.
My pride doesn't allow that.
There is no wedding with our family members present.
There is wedding with the two of us present.
Let's live together. Let's register for marriage license.
I guess something like this is called the common law marriage.
I prepared a proposal on the day we signed the prenuptial agreement.
But you ruined my plans for the day.
I don't believe in the saying I will love you forever.
Minnie Dong Bi who suffers from lack of affection, I will love you forever.
Let's go to Paris for our honeymoon.
You remember our first trip, don't you?
- Mom.
-Grandmother!
Oh my, my puppy is here.
- Where is aunt?
- She's not here yet.
I wonder what kind of announcement she needs to make. She strutting her stuff after getting married.
- She's pregnant.
- What?
I met Uncle. Aunt told him to keep it a secret but he blurted it out.
Oh my. She doesn't miss out on anything.
- It's worth strutting.
- I know.
I am back. Sis is here. Tae Won is here too!
Why did Aunt ask for all the family members to gather?
- She's pregnant.
- Oh my gosh!
- Sis, I am here.
- We're here.
Everyone is here.
- Yeah, Aunt.
- We are here.
Fine, you need to have dinner, right?
- What's wrong?
- What do you mean?
It suddenly turned quiet after I came in.
You're the only noisy one in the family. Why are you picking over nothing?
Stay out of the kitchen. I will call once the dinner is ready.
You guys. I have a major announcement to make today.
- What is it?
- I will tell you later.
- Look forward to it.
- Please look forward.
- Do you know what this is about?
- Huh?
- Of course he knows.
He is a man who has a right to know everything about me. Isn't that right, honey?
Of course.
I will announce it later but everyone has to make a promise.
- What kind of promise?
Don't ever laugh about it.
Why? Why are you laughing?
You don't know what I will say so why are you laughing?
- She's pregnant.
- What?
Grandmother said you're pregnant.
- How did you find out?
- From Hye Jin.
- From uncle.
I asked you to keep it a secret. This is a let down.
Seriously, you love events. What's so great about your pregnancy that you have to make an announcement?
It's a different story if I am the pregnant one.
Mom.
It's all your fault.
It's all because of you. You even cheat on me with another woman.
You could live with her. Why are you acting like this?
What great wrong did I commit during my marriage?
You said family court is to help the divorce process.
- Yeah.
- Helping is a good thing, isn't it?
It's a good thing.
I have a good idea.
- Those are dad's shoes.
- They are. I guess he came home.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to straighten your shoes. I learned it in the kindergarten.
Is Dad in the study?
Probably.
- Dad.
- He's not here.
I guess he went to the bathroom. Let's get you changed first and brush your teeth.
Yes.
I will open the door.
- Dad
- Yeah.
I went to the study. I knew you were home because I saw your shoes.
I see. Where are you coming back from?
- Grandmother's.
- Why are you here?
- Just because.
- Should the three of us sleep together today too?
Let's get changed and wash up.
Can the three of us sleep together?
Yes, we can.
- What are you looking for?
- Alcohol.
Mom got rid of every bottle. It's not here.
Everything is going your way, why are you looking for alcohol?
Is this going my way?
Didn't you see Tae Won? How he's trying to see our reaction?
Well, if you knew about that, you wouldn't behave this way to us.
What do you mean he's trying to gauge our reaction?
Why are you being emotional all of a sudden? Why were in Tae Won's room?
I can't even stay in Tae Won's room?
You're giving him a false hope that we won't get a divorce.
Tae Won thinks we're getting a divorce because he did something wrong.
He thinks things could change if he behaves better.
Is that a way a 7 year old kid should behave?
- So what do you want me to do?
- Let's wrap this up quickly.
Stop holding the kid as a hostage out of spite towards me when you don't know what it means to raise a child.
I have the upper hand from all the evidence relating to this case.
You know that too. You must have met with your lawyer.
When you understand the workings of the kid's mind so well, you don't want to understand what's going inside my heart?
Why do I have to understand you? Did you ever try to understand me?
I am anxious. The anxiety is driving me crazy. I am lonely. The loneliness is driving me crazy.
Everyone is anxious and lonely.
Still they don't turn into a piece of trash like you because of that.
It's alright. Mom's alright, Tae Won.
I want to die.
I was gone from Seoul for just few days and it seems like I was away for quite a while.
That must mean you enjoyed our trip that much, right?
Yes. I was get rid of all the stress I had.
Let's begin the second chapter of our lives.
This is my older sister.
- Oh, unni.
- Why didn't you answer my calls?
I was on a trip and am on my way back.
So many people are just rubbing it in.
What happened?
Ki Joong that rascal got married. He called couple days ago telling me that he's on his honeymoon.
That bi*** deserves to be chewed alive. I warned her very clearly.
Sister, you can't win against your kid.
Are they the type who thinks on the parent's behalf?
They betray you at the critical moment.
- So you should also —
- I guess you patched things up with your husband.
How dare you try to give me your stupid advice?
What's wrong?
Ki Joong married Dong Bi without my sister's knowledge.
What is it about the kid's marriage that makes it
so that our logical abilities are paralyzed, our selfishness surfaces,
my kid's wounds seem to be the biggest one.
- Are you confessing your sins?
- I am just saying that's how it is.
I am not going to bundle my life with my kid's life to hurt my life.
What's so great about my kid?
A marriage starts with a man and a woman
and ends with a man and a woman.
Yes, we are the one who remains. Us two.
What did I tell you? I told you to focus on me.
You're right. I was able to overcome this time because I had you.
If not, I would have made the same decision as Hye Yoon's mom.
- Home sweet home.
- Home sweet home indeed.
This is our kid's wedding invitation.
I guess we need to handle this first. Should I ask Jung Hoon to come home early?
No, I have to take care of Hye Yoon's mom first. I will repay everything with just one punch.
It's here. She's calling. How can she not stand to make concessions?
- Hello.
- How have you been?
Yes, how are you? What's up? You made it seem like you never want to see me again
and you're calling.
I think in life, you act like you never plan to meet each other ever again but you end up meeting again.
Let's meet. We have too many things to talk about over the phone, in-law.
Are you going somewhere?
Jung Hoon's mom called. She wants to meet.
- Why?
- What do you mean why? It's to give her blessing for this marriage.
Jung Hoon is supposed to come over. Once the bed is delivered, we want to rearrange the furniture in this room.
There is no need for that. Your mother-in-law will provide a condo for you to live in.
She won't let her son move in with the in-laws.
Don't get your hopes up. She might just as well say she's deadly against this marriage.
No, that's not it. My gut says so.
She sounded happy.
The condo from Changsi-dong last time has been rented out already.
Will she lease another apartment for you guys?
I just wish she won't oppose the wedding any more.
I just wish she would provide you buys with a place to live and take you guys away.
Earlier you said you will live with us just to show her.
Seeing how you guys bring up rules and guidelines, if I were to live with you guys, I will be the one who will be inconvenienced.
Everything has returned to its proper place.
If your Mother-in-law comes begging and buy you guys a condo,
and asks so you could live on your own, I will play a little hard to get first.
You have grand false hopes. I don't think mother-in-law will do that.
What do you mean she won't? I dealt with her more often than you did.
I know her better than you do.
The report from child psychological evaluation is ready
We will start a proper attack on Mr. Nam Do Hyun.
The report from psychological evaluation is ready
The mom is currently raising the kid and there is no specific reason why the custody should be awarded to the dad.
- It's all set now.
- Does that mean I will get the custody of the child?
Yes. You want to finish this dragged out fight, right?
Yes.
Let's induce settlement from Mr. Nam Do Hyun.
Even if he's not requesting a settlement?
You need to be a bit flexible in cases like this.
His lawyer is aware that Mr. Nam Do Hyun is at a disadvantage in this trial.
Also that it's better for him to settle too.
Then his lawyer will recommend him to settle.
But she cannot strongly tell him to do so to her client.
That might tarnish her reputation too.
How can it be like this?
I told you so already. Unless it's a special circumstance, the custody of child is usually awarded to the mom.
I guess you weren't able to form a special bond with the child from earlier.
- Does that mean I have to settle?
- That's better.
You will lose if we go to the trial.
However, once a verdict is reached at the trial, the verdict will remain in the court files for 40 years.
What does that mean?
If the court or the prosecutors search under your name, your divorce verdict will be available for viewing.
It will be on the record for 40 years.
Isn't it kind of embarrassing? If you are going to give it to her anyway, isn't it better to save the embarrassment?
- How have you been?
- Fine, how have you been?
You look well.
Yes, I just came back from a trip with my husband.
Good.
I am sorry for my earlier behavior.
That's right. I knew she would act this way.
I behaved in a rude manner under the excuse this is for my son and it's to provide a better live to my son.
I will forgive you since you have come to your senses now.
It takes two to tango.
The conflict in the wedding preparation process is not just one person's fault. But both of us is to blame.
You're right.
I heard from Jung Hoon.
Right. She's ready to make concessions now.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
To be honest, in order to provide a house for Jung Hoon's wedding, we would have to stretch our finances a lot.
But you said he could move into your house.
Then, you are planning to have Jung Hoon live with the in-laws?
I didn't decide that. Jung Hoon made the decision to move in with the in-laws.
I have decided to respect his decisions 100% from now on.
This is not the way I wanted it to turn out.
Don't think you're the only one with a brain, Lee Deul Ja.
But still, he's your only son. Aren't you sad to send him away to live with me?
What do you mean disappointed? It's better this way.
Both of them are working and soon they will have a baby. Who will raise the baby then?
You want me to raise the baby too?
Try to raise the baby, I will visit the baby.
Still, weren't you against the marriage? Why the sudden change of a heart?
I choose my husband over the son.
These days everyone seems to forget that I am a widow.
Couples love to rub it in to me.
I didn't mean to. Then, I will get going.
How can you just leave like that?
Then what?
I don't think we had a chance to talk about what's really important.
I am for this marriage.
It's good that you're for it, but are you happy that your son will live with the in-laws?
He will be loved by the mother-in-law and that's great.
We decided to wrap up our life in Seoul within this month to move to the country side.
I shot myself in the foot.
I will see you at the wedding.
This can't be. No, she will change her mind tomorrow.
How can she allow her son to live in the in-laws?
What exactly is going on? Why is she doing this? How can she let go of her son?
What is this? What are the kids doing?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
I think we have to move the desk to Aunt's room.
I agree. The room is too small.
Is everything alright?
Mom, what's wrong? You're pale.
Did Mother-in-law say negative things?
She gave permission for your marriage.
But why do you look like that then?
It's nothing.
No matter how I think about it, she's the last one standing.
Life is really unfair.
If she had an easy life till now, she will continue to have it easy for the rest of her life.
The woman with a hard life till now will continue to have it harsh for the rest of her life.
You seem to be in a good mood.
You should have seen Hye Yoon's mom's face.
I thought about it on the way back, the title match between Hye Yoon's mom and me,
Hye Yoon's mom made many jabs but I landed the decisive punch.
- Are you happy because you defeated her?
- Yes, I am happy.
Do you know this? I didn't have to go to a speech class and I still won.
I may lack in the speaking department but I am more skilled in assessing the situation.
- Congratulations.
- It's thanks to you.
In marriage, it's not just he kids becoming independent from their parents. The parents are also gaining independence from their kids too.
Do you have to insist on working? Aren't you tired?
There are things that needs to be handled. Even if I am tired, I just have to suck it up.
- How about you, honey?
- I have to work too.
Then I will see you later at home.
You're so natural calling it home.
It is home. Our home.
You are a man worthy enough to tolerate your mother.
- I won't miss out.
- Don't miss out.
- Bye.
- Yes.
Mother-in-law, we're back. Please meet me at Ki Joong's house,
like the last time.
Please try again.
You're early.
Hurry and open the door.
You have to stay far away from the door for me to unlock the door.
What?
I don't want to get hit again.
How audacious of you to request to meet with me. How dare you.
You will acknowledge your wedding. If you think things will change as a result, you're mistaken.
The law protects comonlaw marriages too.
You're mistaken but not just the commonlaw marriage, we actually registered our marriage. Without the prenuptial agreement.
I am eligible for the legal protection too.
What?
It's better than before. Thanks to your hand in this.
Now, even if I am chased out of this house, I won't be chased out with just the clothes on my back.
Don't ever touch me.
Since you're the mother of the man whom I love, I will try to accept you as much as I can.
Who's accepting whom?
I said all that needs to be said. This is our home.
If you want to eat a meal, then I will prepare something.
However, I am not a good cook so Ki Joong usually cooks.
- I will learn how to cook.
- How ludicrous.
Tae Won.
Leave him alone.
You have to eat dinner. I told you to wait in the living room but why did you come into your room?
- What?
- Let's talk.
I have nothing to say.
- Let's settle.
- Do it through my lawyer.
We will talk then.
Tae Won.
Dad is not scary.
Dad didn't hit Mom on that day.
We were just playing around.
Dad is a good person.
You can never question that.
When you are playing with your friend, you have sword fight, chicken leg fight.
Mom and Dad were playing around like that too.
Watch. See?
I am holding Dad's hand.
Tae Won should hold Dad's hand too.
Three of us are a family and like the last time, we are holding hands together.
Dad is not a bad person, you know that right?
- Then let's go eat dinner now.
- Yes.
Thank you.
I am not doing this so you could be grateful.
This is all for Tae Won.
I don't want you to fall apart.
Don't fall apart.
I don't want you to fall apart. You should live well.
You're Tae Won's dad.
I hope you live well.
Even though I hate you, I want you to live well.
I don't want you to destroy yourself.
- Do it well.
- I am doing it well.
- How are you doing it well? You're offbeat.
- Did you practice? How come you're so skilled?
I am not skilled. Hold tight.
Right foot. Start.
- Slowly.
- Okay.
I will be officiating this wedding.
I agreed to officiate this wedding because
of what was written on their wedding invitation they gave me.
We got back together after breaking up twice.
We will never let go of each other's hand for the rest of our lives.
The words written from their loving history moved my heart.
I will use their words in lieu of officiant's message.
Don't let go of each other's hands for the rest of your lives.
I think I should have had a wedding ceremony.
Do it now if you want to.
I shouldn't with a baby bump.
I now announce you man and wife in front of God and the people here.
- Don't you regret it?
- No, I like the way how we did it.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Please sit here.
You're the one who put in a lot of effort.
Now we became in-laws and the kids are doing well.
- I am really curious about something.
- What is it?
You ran a background a check, right?
Am I crazy to tell you that?
No, I didn't.
It's alright to say so now. I am just so curious.
You did run a background check.
I didn't.
Before I die, I really want to see admit that she did it
Whether or not you did it or not, how does that matter now?
You did it, right?
I said I didn't.
- You did it, right?
- Oh my gosh.
- I said I didn't do it. Why are you acting like this?
You did do it.
I think they will grow attached.
You grow attached through quarrels.
Do you know that? Those two are the matchmakers and the obstructors of our relationship.
I know. Depending on the perspective, they could be either the matchmakers or the obstructors.
I am saying this since it's over. But if I think about how you made me suffer.
How I did make you suffer?
Do you think you didn't make me upset?
After I calmed my mom down and handled the newlywed house situation and when I though we're finally getting married. You said let's break up.
Do you know how dumbfounded I was then?
You still kept that bottled inside. You know how to hold a grudge.
It's been a while since you pointed out that I hold a grudge. Why aren't you calling me that I am sulking type as you usually do?
I was joking. I guess you really are sulking because I said you hold a grudge.
- Are you sulking?
- Who's sulking?
- You're blaming me again.
- What do you mean blaming you? You do hold a grudge.
If I hold a grudge, you're the wife of the person who hold a grudge. Good for you. Grudge holder wife.
I like it. I really like, what will you do now?
We really frequented here.
I know.
- Good luck.
- Call me before you come to pick up Tae Won next Saturday.
- I will.
What's wrong?
- Mom!
- Why did you make the baby cry?
Honey, hurry and eat. You'll be late for work.
That won't do. Mom, put him on your back.
Why do I have to put him on my back? You have to drop her off at the daycare.
I can't because I am running late. Please drop him off, Mom.
- Hurry and eat.
- I am coming.
Good morning, mother-in-law. Good morning, So Wool.
You only see her?
Don't yell at me.
How many times do I have to tell you? You have a right to scold only me. Don't scold my husband.
He's under a lot of stress from work.
I can't even do this when I cook and you live in my house?
- I will be late.
- Me too.
- Let's hurry and leave.
- I am not done talking.
I understand mom. I will listen in the evening when I get back from work. Please feed the baby before you drop her off at the day care.
I am sorry, Mother-in-law. Bye.
- Mom, I will be back. Bye So Wool.
- Bye, So Wool.
I thought my job is over once she's married.
I was crazy.
I want to go back.